Our Secret
EP04
Jealous.
Good morning.
Xianxian
Dad
Your mom told me that
you want a phone?
How about this?
You use mine first,
and I'll use my old PHS.
No, dad, it's all right.
I have nothing urgent,
but just to keep contact with my classmates.
It's okay for them to call me on
our fixed-line telephone.
Alright.
Invite your classmates
to our home for a dinner
some other day,
to deepen your friendship.
Okay.
It's not your handwriting, right?
It's pretty good.
Yeah, it's Zhou Siyue's.
I nodded off during the English lesson,
and missed the key-points.
So he wrote up the notes for me.
Look at you, falling asleep in class again.
Anyway, it's really nice of Siyue to
exchange seats and write notes for you.
He helped you a lot, right?
Dad
How did you know about exchanging seats?
It can't be you who
let him do all these stuff, right?
No wonder I saw you two talking
downstairs the other day.
So that's why he's been so considerate.
Well, Xianxian
I asked Siyue
for help so that you won't get
-bullied.  -Dad
Stop doing this.
I don't need you to do these things.
I can take care of myself well.
Just leave me alone.
Moreover,
I don't want anyone to do
something they don't like for me.
It's not something
we don't like, Xianxian.
In fact, Siyue and I...
Good morning.
Morning.
Just yourself?
Where's your deskmate?
No idea.
Did you have a quarrel?
No.
We're not that close, anyway.
I'm going for the teacher to recite the text.
Well, look at you.
Did you annoy your deskmate?
She...
She stood me up this morning.
I almost got late for school.
I don't think I have annoyed her.
Truly old friends are like wine,
the older, the better.
Well done.
I can see your efforts.
Keep working.
Thank you.
I remember your deskmate is Zhou Siyue, right?
Go find some time to practice with him.
He's good at spoken English.
Don't be shy.
It's quite normal for classmates
to help each other.
He's already helped me a lot.
Alright, go back now.
Are you serious? I just had one sip of Coke.
I'm so sorry. I...
I didn't mean it. I'm so sorry.
-Just go back to class and wipe it.  -I'm sorry.
Do you have nothing to do?
Let's go, go.
I'm so sorry.
It's okay. I don't need it.
Keep it.
I'm sure you don't want to go back to class like this.
Thank you.
Why didn't you wait for me this morning?
I have known everything already.
It was my dad who asked you to take care of me, right?
That's the reason?
Sorry to trouble you.
You don't have to do these if you don't want to.
What are you laughing at?
Never mind.
You probably don't remember.
What?
Tell me.
I owe you something, in fact.
When I was five,
I went back to my grandpa's home.
I stayed at your home
during the flood, do you remember?
Hey, I wanna go to the toilet.
It's outside there. Go yourself.
You wetted the bed. Shame on you.
There's no toilet.
I couldn't hold it and I...
It's right outside.
I don't know how to use it.
You are old enough to use the toilet.
I'll tell my mom.
Don't do it.
I'll take you out
next time when you're in town.
I can't believe you had such an
embarrassing moment.
You...
Don't you dare say it to anyone.
So where are we going to play around?
What?
You promised.
You are fishing in troubled water.
How could you treat me like this?
At 1:00 pm on Saturday,
wait for me in front of your home.
What did you do last night?
I just couldn't fall asleep.
You seem to be in a good spirit.
Go coach Ding Juncong for math later.
I'm engaged this afternoon.
What things do you have on weekend?
I'm going to school for the blackboard newspaper.
It will be checked next week.
I remember you failed to be
elected as a class committee member.
Just for help.
Don't do it anymore.
It's a thankless job,
and may waste your study time.
Checkmate.
I'll take one move back.
No, no. Don't do this.
-Don't take it back.  -Brother Li.
-You are here, Zhou.  -You are playing chess.
Checkmate.
-Are you sure?  -Checkmate.
You can't take it back, understand?
Excuse me then.
It's my poor eyesight. I didn't see it.
It has been five times, Uncle.
One move, one move.
Only one move.
You're here.
I'm gonna leave now, Uncle.
Enjoy yourself.
Can't take the joke, right?
What's wrong today?
Uncle, I'll take his place.
What's the matter?
It's your fault. You come so late.
You little snail.
Well, I'm a girl.
What's the smell?
Nothing.
Fried chicken wings.
Thank you, Sir.
Okay.
My treat this time.
I'll never let a girl pay the bill.
It seems that you often go out with girls.
How could it be possible?
Just eat.
Are there any good spots in Shenhai?
Good spots?
Maybe the science and technology museum.
The sea theater is okay, too.
I know there's one bridge
from which we can see the beautiful night view.
Long years ago, it was a small fishing village.
As the economy has grown recently,
it gradually thrives.
Sometimes I think you are really excellent.
You know everything and can do everything.
Compared with you,
it's true.
Can't you be a little humble?
Ding Xian
Actually,
when you stop being so one-track minded,
you are quite...
What?
Quite like a normal girl.
I think you are the abnormal one.
Okay.
Inform me in advance
when you wanna go somewhere.
I'll show you around.
Xianxian
Su
Why are you here?
I come to buy some stuff.
This is...
your deskmate?
You are quite close.
Nuh...
I think I have heard of him.
He's Zhou Siyue, right?
You know him?
I've heard of him a lot. He's popular.
By the way, have you listened to the
CD I gave you?
Yes, my teacher praised me for that.
Thanks a lot, Su.
It's all right.
I'll ask Uncle Ding to
bring you some more.
Okay.
Alright,
you can go back now.
Then see you later, bye.
Bye-bye.
Why have you eaten all my fish balls?
I thought you were
too happy to eat.
That does not mean that you can have all of them.
There's only one left.
I'm full.
Let's watch a movie this afternoon, okay?
My treat.
Okay.
What movie do you want to watch?
How about this?
A Hollywood film.
"2012"
Okay, wait a second.
I'll go get the tickets.
Excuse me.
What are you doing?
Thank you.
What's this?
3D glasses.
Haven't you watched it before?
I have.
Of course I have.
Let's go.
Sorry.
Excuse me.
This row.
Siyue
Ding Xian
You
do feel a little upset, right?
Upset about what?
You should be upset.
Idiot.
Now I have returned your favor,
and we are quits then.
And I don't need your help then.
For real?
The final exam is coming.
I'm wondering if there's anyone
coming to ask for my help.
Don't worry. It's not gonna be me.
Ding Xian
It's the class supervisor.
Ding Xian, why are you running?
Ding Xian, stop running.
Hello?
Hello, sir.
Are you interested in buying a house?
No, I'm not.
Maybe you can learn about it first.
It's a very good deal to buy it
with the housing loans.
I don't need the loan either.
Sir, it's okay to learn about the loans
even if you don't buy the house.
What's the point to know about the loans
if I don't buy the house?
Has he gone?
I got a house to live in.
I'm not short of...
Uh, I'm kind of short of money.
Listen, how did you
calculate the interest?
You call this a low rate of interest?
I'm telling you,
I can't be fooled by you.
You know who I am?
I'm a teacher.
I'm a math teacher.
Your numbers...
Keep saying.
It's not right.
Wait a second, hang in there.
Hang in there.
Hello?
Well, tell me about your
rate of interest.
What do you think
of the end of the world
in 2012?
I think there's gonna be an
earthquake, a tsunami,
a volcanic eruption.
Something like that.
Just like what the movie showed.
I don't think so.
Even if we human beings do
face extinction,
we'll face the death
with the last beauty,
with the fireworks
all over the sky.
Could you think of something nice?
Like what we will be
doing in 2012.
I may be enjoying the beauty of
the West Lake in Hangzhou.
It's Hangzhou again.
What about you?
Doing experiments
in Huaqing.
You wanna go to Huaqing University?
Sure.
You are good enough to
be admitted.
What about you?
Don't you wanna go to
see better scenery?
I...
I can't do it.
A bigger goal is more
worthy to challenge.
Moreover,
I have never seen anyone
who works harder than you.
Trust yourself, you can do it.
A word to you:
there's still a light of glory on the other side.
Good one. It's good.
I'll come back later.
You are here.
Good for you, Song.
I'm so tired.
Siyue
How about coming to the countdown party
with Little Monster?
Little Monster.
I thought you don't like her.
Why do you invite her to the party?
It was just a misunderstanding
at the beginning.
It turned out that
she's quite interesting
when she holds her stubborn temper.
What about you, Jiang Chen?
Will you join us?
Why didn't you ask me earlier?
I already have plans.
You just forget us
once you got your new friends in high school.
Look at him, dressing like this
to play basketball here.
I'm so busy.
You are lucky to have me here.
Come on.
Don't fool us around.
Go, just go play yourselves.
Go, let's go.
Leave him alone.
Enjoy yourselves.
What's on the card
from Little Monster?
What card?
Her self-made card.
She sent cards to me and Shadi.
Haven't you received it yet?
I'm leaving now, mom.
Siyue, wait a second.
I heard from Wanxian that Xianxian
has been taking traditional Chinese
medicine to nourish her vitality lately.
Would you like to take some
since you have been working so hard?
I'm okay.
She said it's quite bitter
and quite effective.
Xianxian takes it every day.
Oh yeah?
Morning.
Is it Chinese medicine again made by your mom?
Yes.
My mom said that I need to take it
to nourish my vitality since winter is coming.
You sure need it.
You are too weak,
nodding off in class every day.
I'm not weak, okay?
Just finish it.
Is it really this bitter?
It does taste very bitter.
A candy bar.
Still feel bitter now?
It's blueberry flavor.
I remember you don't like to eat candy.
Go to the class now.
Won't you go with me?
I'm waiting for Song Ziqi
to give him something.
You go first.
Spend the holiday with us tonight, okay?
You know I have no interest in
celebrating holidays.
Stop making an exception any more.
You leave early every year.
Can't we spend the
New Year's Eve together like a family?
Now let's begin the early exercises.
Turn to page six in book seven and read
the text we learned yesterday together.
Where's my card?
I knew it already.
Kong Shadi and Song Ziqi have
both received your cards in advance,
while your deskmate
still has not received your card
on New Year's Eve.
You said you are not a fan of
celebrating holidays, didn't you?
It's the holiday that I don't like,
not the present.
So everyone got it except me.
Zhou Siyue, Ding Xian
Go stand outside.
I never said I didn't prepare for you.
I draw it myself.
The former one was messed by my brother,
so I made a new one.
I know it's a little bit late now.
Don't open it now. Open it when you get back.
Good for you.
So when you were not with us,
you didn't study either.
To use the card-making time, your math
grades can be improved at least 20 scores.
Don't look a gift horse in the mouth.
Give it back to me if you don't want it.
Give me that.
You two
come to my office now.
You are required to copy the text ten times?
It's scaring.
15 times.
You ran into auntie during the rebuking.
So there're five times more.
It's really unlucky of you two.
He is now in climacteric.
You should thank god since he
didn't let you do examination papers.
Xianxian, what do you do on the New Year's Day?
How about hanging out together?
We'll talk about it later.
I haven't received the results
of the math quiz last time.
Come on, you didn't join us last time.
I was so bored
to hang out
with them.
How about this?
I'll go with you if I do well
in the math exam
this afternoon.
Really?
Then it's a deal.
God bless you to get a high grade in the exam.
Come on, one more bite.
They provide you energy to copy.
It's already over
to trust her.
Shut up.
What?
You felt boring to go out with us?
We don't even wanna take you out.
Right, Siyue?
You can't blame Shadi.
You were sort of boring, in fact.
Come on, you're hurting my feelings.
You seem like really enjoy
eating my foods.
I can't see you're hurt.
Sorry, I'm
just sharing your burden
in case you get too tired.
That's sweet.
Why don't you help me with the copying
since you wanna share my burden?
I'm just a little hungry right now.
Well,
our handwritings are quite different.
You've eaten all the meat.
Alright, I'll do it.
Don't laugh at my poor handwriting.
Come here, Deng Wanwan.
Help me to give the papers out.
Xianxian
How's your exam?
Stop asking.
I can't go out with you.
You've improved a lot.
Let me see it.
Your score is twice higher than hers.
Alright.
Stop talking now.
Look at your scores.
Do you still have the nerve to talk around?
Won't you be worried?
As the holiday is coming,
your hearts are already not
in school, right?
Being late for school,
sleeping during class,
and talking during lessons,
you really impress me a lot.
For this semester,
some of you learned nothing but the
talking skills with your
surrounding classmates.
Your mouths just never stop.
All I hear is your murmuring.
The seats will be rearranged
right after the final exam.
I'll see how you will chat in this way.
Sit back.
No one can leave
without my word.
Take out your papers now.
Sighing for what?
I owe you nothing.
Look at the last but one question on your paper.
The 17th.
It's worth ten points.
We're gonna change seats next semester.
Where are you gonna find
such a nice deskmate as me?
Stop flattering yourself.
Are you really gonna stay at home
for this whole holiday?
Didn't he say you have improved a lot?
It's far from a lot.
It's only two places above
my former one.
The score and the rank are different.
No one can make huge progress in such a short time.
You'd better relax yourself rather
than keep pushing yourself like this.
Moreover, I remember that you said
it's good enough to raise for one place.
Now you changed your mind.
The final exam is coming
right after the holiday.
I'm thinking that next semester...
What?
I wanna make it easier for the next semester.
I have already been left behind.
From Senior One to Senior Three,
it's a short period.
Easier?
Alright.
Listen, it's just Senior One now.
Let me remind you.
It can only get harder, not easier.
Listen to me,
the college entrance examination
is a narrow bridge for
millions of people to cross.
Okay.
You remember this line quite clear.
But
stop pretending to work hard,
all of you.
The results can't lie to you.
Alright.
This holiday only has three days,
which are not a period for you to relax.
If anyone makes the same mistakes
once again after the holiday,
copy it ten times.
Do you understand?
Yes.
You are dismissed.
The class is over.
Come on, let's go.
Go. Let's go.
The seats will be rearranged
right after the final exam.
I'll see how you will chat in this way.
To work harder, if I don't want a new deskmate.
Look at the young couple,
they are perfect for each other.
Xianxian did not step out of her room
for the whole day.
Is there anything wrong?
I'll have a look.
All other parents are only too anxious
to see their kids working hard.
Look at you, all you do
is keeping bothering her.
She should alternate work with rest.
Besides, it's on holiday now.
Don't fuss.
She'll get out herself when she's tired.
Just leave her alone.
Here,
eat this.
Mom, I wanna go out to set off fireworks.
No.
I don't care. I'm going out.
Keep your voice down.
I'm going out.
I'm setting off fireworks.
Hush, stop shouting.
Alright, alright.
Just take him out
since he wants the fireworks.
It's quite lively out there.
Well, it's a good time for Xianxian
to relax herself.
Wait a second, I'll go get your sister.
Okay, okay.
All you know is playing.
Xianxian
Okay, take a picture now.
It goes out very soon.
Hurry up.
Do I look good with this posture?
Yeah.
Really?
You go down a little.
Like this?
No.
Just have a look to see if I look good.
Okay. I'm looking at it. You look great.
You didn't look.
I did.
Have you taken my legs?
Hurry up. It's going out.
Okay, look at it.
What's that?
You told me to squat down.
Where's my face?
So what now?
It's going off now.
Buy me a new one.
Alright. I'll get you a new one.
All is yours.
Practice taking photos here.
Broke again.
You ask for it.
I have no choice.
You know, we grow up together.
Everyone would know when she throws a hissy fit,
and it's my job to amuse her.
You know about Pavlov's dog, right?
I'm the dog.
I'm not sure about the conditional reflex.
But you are indeed like a dog.
I'll bite you to death.
Hey, it's almost 12 o'clock.
Set off the fireworks now.
Not in the mood?
What's wrong?
Too few people.
I can't help feeling bored.
You want Little Monster to be here, right?
I get it now, Mr. Zhou.
You don't want her to feel lonely
at home, right?
It's not the thing.
So who do you wanna call?
Come on, tell me.
I'm trying to make you feel better
to invite Ding Xian.
What do you mean?
Think about this.
Kong Shadi will feel happy
once she comes, right?
They'll play together
and you'll be free.
Then we two...
Mr. Zhou, good for you.
Right, right.
Look, Song Ziqi,
I got two different one.
Great.
Other kids must envy you.
Let's go.
Let's go now.
Where to go?
Go find you a cameraman.
Xianxian
We go to watch the firework show with Congcong.
There are fruits on the table.
Suit yourself and don't get too tired.
Call us
if you wanna come.
I also want to watch it with everyone.
Little Monster
Ding Xian
Come out!
What are you doing here?
They said they won't go to watch the fireworks
without you.
Don't pass the buck to me.
Right, get down now.
Well, it's almost 12 o'clock.
We'll catch a cold
if you don't get down right now.
I'm coming.
We won't make it.
We may miss the fireworks show?
You would catch it if you didn't come to me.
It's all right.
Look at the traffic,
we can go somewhere else in fact.
Isn't it
too late now?
Get off the car now, and I have an idea.
Come on, keep the changes.
I know there's a place.
We can make it.
Let's go.
Go, go.
I'm so sorry.
It's okay.
The traffic is quite heavy anyway.
And we've seen it just now.
Look!
Oh my god, look. Fireworks.
Fireworks.
Awesome.
Happy New Year!